Scott, Leonard Collection of Union Carbide Labor Documents 6314
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Leonard Scott Collection of Union Carbide Labor Documents
1949-2010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Scott, Leonard
Czarnecki, Lottie
Czarnecki, Thaddeus
Union Carbide
Oil, Chemical and Atom Workers' Union
Bakery and Confectionary Workers' International Union of America
6314
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Records.
7198353
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives 227 Ives Hall Tower Road Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheelref@cornell.edu https://catherwood.library.cornell.edu/kheel/
Compiled by:
R. Miles, May 10, 2011
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 07, 2016
Chemical industry -- Employees -- Labor unions; Czarnecki, Lottie; Czarnecki, Thaddeus; Scott, Leonard; Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America; Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union; Union Carbide Corporation
7198353
- The Smackdown of the American Worker: How It Happened and What Should Be Done About It, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Self-published book by Leonard C. Scott.
- Union Carbide Crystal Products Plant, Telegram and Letter., 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  East Chicago, IL. Letter is a photocopy.
- Union Carbide Crystal Products Plant, Strike., 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  East Chicago, IL.
- Union Carbide Crystal Products Plant, Negotiations., 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Union Carbide Crystal Products Plant and the Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Agreement., 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  East Chicago, IL. Photocopy.
- Union Carbide Crystal Products Plant, Communications. [folder 1 of 3], 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  East Chicago, IL. Mostly photocopies.
- Union Carbide Crystal Products Plant, Communications. [folder 2 of 3], 1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Union Carbide Crystal Products Plant, Communications. [folder 3 of 3], 1962-1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union Organizing Manual (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Photocopy.
- Lottie Czarnecki Correspondence, 1949-1955 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Mother of Leonard C. Scott.
- Lottie Czarnecki's Union Card from the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Union. (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Thaddeus Czarnecki's Dues Books from the Bakery and Confectionary Workers International Union of America, 1954-1955 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Father of Leonard C. Scott.
- Thaddeus Czarnecki's Union Cards from the Bakery and Confectionary Workers International Union of America, 1959-1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Bakery and Confectionary Workers International Union of America Union Pins (Box 1, Folder 14)
  3 pins likely from Thaddeus Czarnecki, father of Leonard C. Scott.